(Raj:)How about the girl from
The Wonder Years?
(Howard:)Gentlemen, I believe I've found the solution
to all our problems.
(Leonard:)We can't ask Leslie Winkle.
(Raj:)Why? Because you slept together...
(Raj:)...and when she was done with you,
she discarded you like last night's chutney?
(Leonard:)Yes.
- You gotta take one for the team.
- Yeah. Sack up, dude.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Leonard:)Here I go, taking one for the team...
(Leonard:)...in the sack.
(Leonard:)- Hey, Leslie.
- Hi, guys.
Ahem. So, Leslie,
I have a question for you...
(Leonard:)...and it might be a little awkward,
you know, given that I...
Hit that thing.
(Leslie:)There's no reason to feel uncomfortable
because we've seen each other's faces...
(Leslie:)...and naked bodies contorted
in the sweet agony of coitus.